# Raymond Gakwaya

Hello! I'm a tech enthusiast, full stack developer, and I am passionate about software development and IT in general. I have an experience in software development, below are a few noteworthy experiences in my career so far

KN 12 Street, Muhima Kigali City, (250) 789932381 raymond42.gr@gmail.com

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Andela**, Kigali-Rwanda — Full-Stack Software Engineer

July 2019 - April 2020

Andela provides companies with access to the top 1% of global tech talent. They identify high-potential developers on the African continent, shape them into world-class technical leaders, and pair them with companies as full-time, distributed team members.

Andela developers work as full-time engineers with companies ranging from the Fortune 500 to high-growth startups.

# **LifeStores HealthCare** , Lagos-Nigeria — Backend Software Engineer

Nov 2019 - Feb 2020

Lifestores Healthcare aims to be the leading pharmaceutical retail company for the Nigerian mass market. I was working in a remote agile team development to build a pharmaceutical software called HealthId.

# TIGO, Kigali-Rwanda — Sales & Marketing officer

2017 - 2018

Tigo which now emerged with Airtel, offers phone services like – prepaid, postpaid, mobile internet, broadband. I worked there as an internet broadband sales & marketing officer.

### **PROJECTS**

# **Authors Haven** — Full-stack Developer, DevOps

Authors Haven was an Andelan project which was for creating a community of like minded authors to foster inspiration and innovation by leveraging the modern web. I worked as a full-stack developer and also DevOps of this project.

Stack: PREN(Postgres, React, Express, Node js)

### **Converge** - Backend Developer

Converge is an Andela internal product that manages the availability and use of Andela meeting rooms.

Stack: Python/Flask

# **HealthID**- Backend Developer

HealthID is an Inventory Management and Customer Engagement software platform designed for Pharmacists/Chemists and their Customers.

Stack: Python/Django

#### **EDUCATION**

# **OpenClassrooms,** Paris – France — *Software Development Certificates*

July2018 - Feb 2019

OpenClassrooms is an online platform offering top quality, education-to-employment programs and career coaching services for students worldwide. I obtained six certificates in software development with Javascript.

# **Groupe Scolaire De Gahini,** Kayonza District— High School Diploma

January 2014 - December 2016

#### **OTHER CERTIFICATES**

**Andela Bootcamp Certificate** This is a technical workshop that qualifies a person with skills in web development and in soft skills with EPIC values(Excellence, Passion, Integrity, and Collaboration).

**Leadership Skills Certificate.** December 2014, I obtained a certificate in leadership skills from Youth Impact Mission (YIM) conference, a students' conference held at King David Academy Kanombe

### Video Production and Photography Certificate.

I obtained a certificate in photography and video production from Kigali International Art College

### **SKILLS**

- NodeJs
- React
- React native
- Python
- Django
- Flask
- GraphQL
- SQL
- Docker
- AWS
- DevOps

### **LANGUAGES**

English, Kinyarwanda

### **REFEREES**

### Joshua TAHINDUKA

Team Skills Learning Facilitator, Andela Rwanda <u>joshua.tahinduka@andela.com</u>

Tel: +250788663464

### Bernard DUSHIMIMANA

Technical Manager, Andela Rwanda bernard.dushimimana@andela.com

Tel: +250782769303